Praise the Lord!
Children of God..Praise the Lord!
If you are happy to be in the presence of God put your hands together for our Lord Jesus.
If you believe today is the day that the Lord has made in your life, put your hands together for our Lord Jesus!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Greet your neighbor: "Good morning." Greet your neighbor: "Good morning"
Viewers all over the world we want to greet you once again: "Good morning in Jesus name."
Good morning to your health
Good morning to your business. Good morning to your career
Good morning to your destiny. Good morning to your life in Jesus name"
Hallelujah! You may be seated in the presence of God.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tell your neighbor: "It is a new dawn."
It is a new dawn.
The Bible says that if anything is in Christ.
is a new creation in
In the mind of God..
old man has stopped being....
The new man...
has taken his place.
My name is Gingka.
And today by the grace of God, I want to tell you that whatever unpleasant situation that you may be facing..
whatever seems impossible in your life
Get ready
Because the Holy Spirit will make it possible in Jesus name.
In the book of Genesis chapter 1 verse 3
When God said. "et there be light."
The Bible says he trusted His Word..
and there was light.
He's the King of Kings and the Lord of Lords.
He was not speaking out of things that were already in existence.
But of things that are yet unseen.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Things that look naturally impossible.
His expression showed..
that whatever God ordered or
or decreed out of faith..
came into being.
I don't know the challenges that you are facing this morning brethren.
And I don't know the mountain that just surrounds you.
But I tell you if you can exercise that absolute faith that God had in His Word..
When creating you..
You can set your Mountain
move with faith in your heart
Without doubt, you will move the impossible.
Talking about trust.
Trust, moves the impossible.
Trust..
Moves the impossible.
The Bible says that everyone is endowed with something within.
That needs to be transferred to the outside.
You have been endowed with something within.
It is easy to say: "I have faith man. And continue to hope for years.
As long as you continue hoping, the Bible says it will always be beyond you
until you add substance to your hope and receive Christ by faith.
The Bible says that faith is the substance of things hoped for.
Faith is the substance of things we hope for.
Faith and hope, the Bible says, go together.
The problem of our faith brethren is not far from the fact that we fail to add substance to our hope..
and receive Christ by faith.
And that is why the book of James says that faith
Is to be expressed through works..
Faith without works, the Bible says, is dead.
But don't forget that, it is your work that confirmed that, faith is alive and active in you.
It sees your actions that confirm the faith is alive and active in you.
It is your deeds that confirm that faith is alive and active in you.
Therefore faith is perfected by our acting on the Word of God.
You see faith can be likened to the soup you prepare in your various forms.
I know we have a lot of shelves in the house.
We have a lot of people who know how to make soup.
Those ingredients you put together to make soup.
Are all the Bible refers to as substance.
I really want to ask one or two people here..
if you can just tell us..
if you would like to make..
local dish.. I mean soup..
Can you tell us what are the two three ingredients you put together to make a soup.
I believe you are going to represent..
all the good cooks, good chefs here. Tell us one or two three ingredients you put together.
Well, I like tomato soup so I will take onions and also..
chicken what I like... and...
Maggie
That is good.
You see our sister just told us about four different ingredients that she, on her own,
will put together to make
beautiful soup.
You know you can make your soup in different ways and still have your wonderful results.
Now in faith..
Those ingredients you put together..
I mean those substances that you put together to make a right result..
in faith the Bible refers to them as trust..
Does Maggie.. chicken you are talking about.. the Bible refer to them as..
confidence..
obedience..
patience.. perseverance.. endurance-
These are the instrument of faith.
The Bible refers to them as works.
Today we want to move impossibilities in our lives.
But we fail to consider those ingredients;
tose substances that we need to activate our faith.
Our hearts desire breakthrough.
But we don't seem to understand that we need to add those substances.. those ingredients.
to activate our faith.
In the book of Genesis 15, the Bible says that Abraham understood this principle.
When God promised that He is going to father many nations.. at his old age.
The Bible says he trusted God; that God would keep His Word.
What God valued in Abraham was the trust he had in his ability to do the impossible.
Abraham trusted God...
that God would do the impossible and that was what God valued so much in him.
Tell your neighbor: "Trust..
Trust..
more the impossible.
And that would be the title of our message today.
And I would like to go to the Book of James chapter 2 as our true text.
The book of James chapter 2. And let's take our reading from verse 14.
Now I read.
What are the profit, my brethren..
If someone says he has faith, but does not have works?
Can faith save him?
If a brother or sister is naked and destitute of daily food...
And one of you said to them: "Depart in peace."
"Be warmed and filled." But you do not give them the things which are needed for the body?
What does it profit?
Does also faith, by itself, if it does not have works is dead.
But someone would say:
"You have faith..
and I have works.
Show me your faith without your works and how I show you my faith by my works?
You believe that there is one God.
You do well.
Even the demons believe..
and... tremble.
But if you want to know, oh foolish man, that faith without works is dead.
Was not Abraham, our Father, justified by works when he offered Isaac, his son, on the altar?
Do you see that faith was working together with his works? And by his works, faith was made perfect.
Verse 23..
And the Scripture was fulfilled which says
Abraham believed God. And it was accounted to him for righteousness.
And he was called "the friend.. of God."
The last verse for this..
protests?
Verse 24...
You see then that a man is justified by works and not by faith alone.
Tell your neighbor: "A man is justified by works.."
I will be justified by my works..
and not by faith alone.
You see...trusting in God...
does not consist in prayer alone.
There are times that we pray in faith.
And there are times that we aren't in faith.
I mean there are things that we must do ourselves.
And others we expect from God.
There are things that we must do ourselves.
And there are some things that we will expect from God.
We all have sent our petitions to God.
We all have sent our requests..
our hearts desire to God.
It is high time for you to sit back in faith to hear what God has to say..
about your situation.
In those processes..brethren..
you need to add trust.
You need to add..
patience..
perseverance.. obedience..
a substance to your hope.. and activate your faith.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Prophet TB Joshua says: "prayer for any special objects.."
must be followed by an absolute trust in the Father...
that he is walking out the answer."
Prayer for any special objects..
Because faith is not a legalistic formula..
created and accepted by man.
Faith..
is not a legalistic formula
created and accepted by man
God's response to faith and not formula.
Faith is not an issue of ordering God around as many do today.
How do I mean?
We are ordering God around when we do not know God's will for our lives and we continue to pray.
Remember God's will means God's promises for our lives. That is why you see people murmuring
complaining
When the answer to their prayers seems to delay in coming.
They begin to seek for shortcuts...
alternatives... bits in the gun..
Brethren..
You must always understand that when God is executing His plans..
in your life..
He also designs and arranges events..
which will continue to unfold..
until his purpose is revealed in your life.
Now take note of this:
God promises.
I know God must have promised us a lot of things
God promises..
He, Himself..
also
designs..
he creates..
He plans..
before..
fulfilling those promises in your life.
He designs events..
of your life as Christians.
Those events could be the unpleasant situation that you are going through.
I mean.. those plans.. could be..
the challenges.
Persecution..
that you may be going through right now.
Brethren..if God allowed it as they did to Job and the host of others
Do not think it strange and doubt your God.
If God allowed it..
you must not consider it unusual or abnormal.
If God allowed that unpleasant situation you must not consider it odd..
and begin to question your faith.
Because when some does not see beyond the immediate situation..
you know as man..
they want to plan themselves.
Because they can't wait for God's time.
They wants to design themselves.. if possible.. execute their own plan themselves.
Whereas they are the work..
of art.
The Book of Genesis..
Chapter 22, the Bible says that Abraham
Moved and did the impossible.
When God instructed him to sacrifice his only child..
Abram knew that Isaac was a child of promise.
Abram realized that God will not delight Himself..
in breaking the covenant ..
by killing the object of His promise.
And that is why when Isaac asked his father in that verse 7..
He said: "Father..
You said we are going for sacrifice.."
"But..
this is food..
And this is fire.. but father, tell me, where is the lamb for the offering?"
Abram said to Isaac.
He said: "My son..
The Lord would provide for Hmself..
the lamb
for the offering.
The Bible says immediately the Holy Spirit affected His word.
And His word became an instrument of victory.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Obeying God at first..
seems hard..
until we come to realize that all He asks is for our good
He makes life full and free for us.
Tell your neighbor: "It honors God to believe Him."
It' honors God to believe Him.
Even while every sense contradicts him
Even while every sense contradicts Him.
For example, we have seen someone who had been promised..
of being a bank manager..
and finally he receives a sack letter as a clerk
Little did he know that that sack letter was to reveal the purpose of God for his life
We have seen many gardeners..
who finally became..
managing directors of companies.
We have seen.. a prisoner..who finally became a president of a nation.
We have indeed seen as servant..
who yesterday..
Who finally became a leader today.
Tell your neighbor: "It honors God..
it honors God..
So believe Him..
everyone.. every sense..
contradicts Him.
What is your situation?
Remember, crossing the Red Sea was an impossible task, in the natural.
The Bible says the Red Sea was against..
the free movement of the Israelites into the Promised Land.
The Red Sea was against their success.
The Red Sea was against their free movement.
But Moses looked beyond it.
And moved the impossible.
I wanted to begin to say right now with faith in your hearts
That whatever Red Sea stands against me and my success..
Say it with all your heart.. because the only spirit will affect your word right now
and that word will become an instrument..
Say: "Whatever Red Sea stands against me and my success..
Whatever Red Sea that stands against me and my freedom..
Whatever Red Sea that stands against me and my success..
In the name of Jesus Christ give way!
In the name of Jesus Christ, begin to give way!
Say it with all your heart!
Because only the spiritual will affect you right now..
and that word..
will bring about your victory today in the name of Jesus Christ!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
In Jesus' mighty Name!
For those who want to see before they believe..
I want to tell you.. remember what the Bible says in the Book of John 20 verse 29..
that "Blessed are those who have not yet seen but believe."
For faith based on what is seen, lacks the quality of being stable
2 Corinthians 5 verse 7 says: "We walk by faith and not by sight."
It is faith that sees the invisible.. what the ordinary eyes cannot see
It is faith..
that move the impossible..
It is faith that receives the incredible.
Tell your neighbor: "Trust..
"Trust and move the impossible."
Trust..
moves the impossible..
in Jesus name!
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Remember the Jewish brothers in the Book of Daniel 3
The Bible says: "A believing heart...
produces right behavior.
Good words as a proof of faith.
A believing heart..
produces right behavior.. good words.. as the proof of faith
Right words..
Right behavior..
that honor Jesus.
reveals that faith is already launched in the hearts..
In Daniel 3 from verse 17 to 18..
When Nebuchadnezzar threatened Shadrach Meshach and Abednego with fire
The Bible says: "They trusted the god of the impossibilities."
and that is why they were bored to say to the king
Oh King, we want you to know
that If we are thrown inside this very furnace..
Our God is able
more than able, to rescue us, to deliver us and to set us free,.
But, If he does not..
we want you to know, oh majesty, that we will not serve your gods or your image that you have set up
The Bible says: "The Holy Spirit affected their word."
That word..
that they spoke..
rose above the law of nature.
and turned the fiery furnace ice cold
Because that word was spoken from the heart.
The Word of God in their hearts..
rose above the law of nature and
and turned the fiery furnace ice cold.
So brethren, what is your situation?
I don't know the unpleasant circumstances that you are facing right now.
I don't know the mountain surrounding you. I
I don't know the situation in your career or perhaps you have received a report that says it is incurable
But I want you to know one thing.
The Word of God on your lips today as believer would rise against the law of nature..
and make that impossibility in your life possible in the name of Jesus Christ in the name of Jesus Christ!
Remember the Word of God is sharper than the two edged sword.
When you experience situations, bretheren, that seem..
contrary to the promise of God for your life..
always remember it is an opportunity to cultivate an attitude of Christ Jesus
Because as far as belief, test and trial will come..
and when it comes..
It is an opportunity for you to cultivate an attitude of Christ Jesus. Stay focused.
Become.
Don't take a step back.
Stay steady.
Even when everything around you is unsteady
Always remember that there is always light at the end of the tunnel
You see, the test that comes from Jesus, always helps our character development
The Bible says: "God often times use these hard times to produce..
maturity..
humility..
in us.
God often times uses hard times
to produce..
maturity, humility and completeness, in us.
So that we can share in his holiness..
and be equipped to enjoy..
the peace and righteousness in Christ Jesus.
Viewers all over the world..
those who are under the influence of these telecasts..
the way out..
The first step of our work of faith is to stop our own work.
To stop our own plan, and rest on God's love, God's power and God's wisdom
Tests and trials will come..
as long as we live.
But when it comes..
Don't be troubled.
Be focused.
Be steady.
Even when everything around you is unsteady.
Finally, brethren..
Turn with me quickly to the Book of Hebrews, chapter 12.
And let's quickly take our reading from verse
1 to 2
"Therefore we also since we are surrounded by so great a cloud..
of weaknesses.
Let us lay aside every weight and the sin which so easily..
ensnares us..
And let us run with endurance, the race that is set before us."
verse 2
"Looking unto Jesus, the author and finisher of our faith..
who for the joy that was set before Him endured the cross..
despising the shame..
that He has sat down at the right hand of the throne of God.
Praise the Lord.
Brethren..
it is the right time..
for you to identify..
Those things that may hinder your movements towards God.
We are in the presence of God.
Remember it is not all up to God and certainly it is not all up to you.
It is high time that we sit down..
to identify those things..
That may hinder our movements towards God.
It could be impatience.
It could be disobedience.
It could be..
anger.
It could be insensitive words..
perhaps..
hatred.
Identify them.
aAnd I pray the Holy Spirit will help our weakness and journey to the strength of God in Jesus name.
No matter what your yesterday was like..
tell anybody the best is yet to come.
No matter what my yesterday was like..
The best is yet to come.
Indeed ,the best is yet to come.
Brethren..
I want to use this opportunity to thank my father in the Lord..
whom God is using mightily..
in the entire world.
For his endless efforts..
In my life..
I never believed..
I can be part of this glorious grace.
Because I am an embodiment of the impossible.
Here I am today.
All Glory..
to His name.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
There is hope!
Brethren, Jesus is the hope.
That same God...
that turned my misery into success today..
That turned my name..
to success..
which turned every impossibility in your life possible in the name of Jesus.
I say that´s the God..
Who turned your failure to success in the name of Jesus Christ.
That same God will turn your sickness into good health.
That same God..
Who turned your mess..
into a message.
in the name of Jesus Christ.
That same God..
would turn..
your tests into a testimony.
in the name of Jesus Christ!
May the Lord bless His Word in Jesus name!
TT: Jacqueline Margaret